RAJNIDUA

ABOUTME

I am a recent coding bootcamp graduate with a passion for developing scalable web applications and working across the full stack. Built fully functional web applications by integrating third party APIs in Javascript. Worked in agile team and made sure that the biggest impact features are worked on first.

EDUCATION

01/05/2021: Coding Bootcamp(Full Stack Developer), University of Adelaide

28/10/2020: Responding to abuse and neglect Education and care full day training

27/10/2020: Intro to Data Analytics (General Assembly)

05/2020 – 06/2020: INCO Academy, Australia (Get INTO TECH PROGRAM for Wordpress, HTML, CSS, Digital Marketing)

02/2020 - 03/2020: HTML5, BootStrap CSS, JavaScript (W3Schools)

01/2018 - 05/2018: A Small Car Sales Project in C# Dot Net

2003-2007: Bachelor in Computer Science and technology(B.Tech) from Kurukshetra University(India)

Experience

Open Roads CC 06/2020 - 11/2020

Website Developer

Currently, I did internship at Open Roads CC. I was responsible for developing the website https://www.AdvCompass.com/India. This website is developed in WordPress. To fulfill certain requirements, I have used CSS and PHP coding in this website.

Infosys Technologies, India 2011-2013

Senior System Engineer

I was responsible for Migration and redevelopment of suite of complex reports originally developed in Actuate / Siebel Environment into Oracle BI Publisher and Siebel 8.1. We developed reports in RTF templates, imported them in BI Publisher Applications, used SQL queries to fetch data needed for the reports and used the BIP application for sending automated bulk emails

Infosys Technologies, India 2007-2010

System Engineer

I worked on the creation of transaction history, export reports, hierarchy difference reports (with validations and verification) using Oracle Hyperion DRM tool across various dimensions like product, channels, unit, account, reporting level etc. for the company "Kraft, EU".

(+61) 0499176910 • rajni.dua14@gmail.com • North Plympton, South Australia